http://www.filmequipment.at/privacy-policy

1.1. General
We process your data exclusively on the basis of the legal provisions according to the DSGVO, the DSG, BDSG and the TKG. The operator of the website named in the imprint is responsible within the meaning of Art 4 Z 7 DSGVO. Since the protection of your personal data is of special concern to us, below we will inform you about the most important aspects of data processing within the framework of our website.
1.1.1. Purpose of processing
The data is processed and stored for the purpose of operating an informal and representative website.
1.1.2. Storage
The data will be set inactive after the discontinuation of the purpose or at the request of the person concerned and will be blocked or permanently deleted, unless the statutory retention periods contradict.
1.1.3. Legal basis of processing
The data are published in the course of our legitimate interest in accordance with Art 6 para 1 lit. f DSGVO. In doing so, we aim to provide the broadest possible representation of our company and thus provide users with the best possible service.
1.1.4. Categories of data
We process personal data in the form of the representation of a website, of pictures as well as if necessary moving pictures, logos as well as free texts.
4.1.5. Categories of recipients
The data will be made available to the respective user of the website. These are consumers as well as entrepreneurs.
4.1.6. Source of the data
The data comes from the person responsible
1.2. Liability of users
All users are obliged to comply with laws, in particular the Data Protection Act, and to indemnify and hold the operator of this website harmless. The use of contact data published by third parties for the purpose of sending unsolicited advertising and information materials is hereby expressly excluded. The operator of the website expressly reserves the right to take legal action in the event of unsolicited promotional information, such as spammails. For the use of this website, the provision of personal data such as name, address or e-mail address is not required. We only collect and store this data if and insofar as you voluntarily make it available to us (for example, when registering for a newsletter).
1.3. Cookies
If the user uses this website, cookies may be set on the user's computer. A cookie is a small text file with letter and number codes stored on the user's web browser on the hard disk of the computer or on the device used. This storage process can be prevented by setting the user on his computer or his terminal. The data obtained in this way does not contain a personal reference. This data is used for marketing and statistical purposes and to optimize the online-service.
Our website uses, among others, offers from the following providers:
1.3.1. Facebook Privacy Notice
This site may use plug-ins from Facebook (Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA). The plug-ins are labeled with a Facebook "f", a "Share" button, or a "Like" button. An overview of the Facebook plug-ins can be found here: https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins.
When using the plug-in, e.g. By pressing the "Share" button, this information is automatically sent to Facebook by users' browsers and stored there. The operator of this website has no influence on the processing of this information by Facebook. For more information, see the Facebook Privacy Policy at https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation.
In order to avoid that their personal data are transmitted to Facebook and assigned to their Facebook account, users should log out of Facebook before visiting the website.
1.3.2. Google Plus Privacy information
This site may use Google Plus plug-ins. The plug-ins are marked with a GooglePlus "g +" button. An overview of the Google Plus plug-ins can be found here: https://developers.google.com/+/web.
When using the plug-in, e.g. By pressing the "g +" button, this information is automatically sent to Google by the user's browser and stored there. The operator of this website has no influence on the further processing of this information by Google. For more information, see the Google Privacy Policy at https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en.
To avoid having their personal information submitted to Google and associated with their Google Account, users should log out of Google before visiting the site.
1.3.3. reCAPTCHA
To protect contact forms on our site, we use the reCAPTCHA service of Google Inc, 1600 Amphitheater Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google"). The query is used to distinguish whether the input is made by a human or abusive by automated, mechanical processing. It includes the sending of the IP address and any other data required by Google for the reCAPTCHA service to Google. For this purpose, your input will be transmitted to Google for further processing. Google uses the information obtained to digitize books and printed materials and to update services such as Google Street View and Google Maps.
The IP address submitted by your browser as part of reCAPTCHA will not be merged with other data provided by Google, unless you are logged in to your Google Account at the time you use the reCAPTCHA plug-in. To prevent the transfer and storage of your information, you must log out of Google before visiting our site using the reCAPTCHA plug-in.
This data is subject to Google's different privacy policies, which are available at https://www.google.com/policies/privacy.
1.3.4. Conversion measurement with the Facebook visitor action pixel
The "visitor action pixel" of Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave., Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA ("Facebook") may be incorporated into our website. This allows us to track the actions of users who have seen or clicked on this Facebook ad, and to track the effectiveness of the Facebook ads for statistical and market research purposes. The data are anonymous and do not contain any personal data of the individual users. These data are still stored and processed by Facebook. Facebook can connect this data with your Facebook account and
also for own advertising purposes, according to Facebook's Data Usage Policy (https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy). You can enable Facebook and its affiliates to display ads on and off Facebook. It may also be stored for these purposes, a cookie on your computer. If the pixel has been installed on this website, you will automatically find a deactivation link in the imprint under "Datenschutz / ANB".
1.3.5. Twitter's Privacy Notice
Our website may use Twitter social media plug-ins operated by Twitter Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA. The plug-ins are provided with a Twitter logo (blue bird). When using the plug-in, e.g. By pressing the "Tweet" button, this information is automatically sent to Twitter by the user's browser and stored there. We have no control over the amount of data Twitter collects using this plug-in. If you are logged in to Twitter, Twitter can assign the visit to your Twitter account. Please refer to the privacy policy of Twitter: https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en for your rights and options for protecting your privacy. To avoid having their personal information transmitted to Twitter and associated with their Twitter account, users should log out of Twitter before visiting the site
1.3.6. Google fonts
On this website external fonts, so-called "Google fonts" are implemented. The integration of these web fonts is done by a server call, which is regularly a Google server in the US. In this case, information is transmitted to the server which of our internet pages you have visited. In addition, the IP address of the browser of the terminal of the user of this website is stored by Google. For more information about Google Fonts, visit https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq and the Google Privacy Policy: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy.
1.4. Third-party cookies
In addition, the inclusion of third party content (Google Maps, DoubleClick, Iframes, etc.) may set cookies that are beyond our control. In order to prevent this process, you may change your browser settings (see under "Objection"). As soon as e.g. If a YouTube video was included, the embedded clip could set cookies on users' computers or devices when they access the page. Furthermore, social media plug-ins are included on our pages in order to recommend and share articles on social networks such as Facebook, Twitter etc. For this a two-stage procedure is used. Data to third parties will not be transferred until the user clicks on one of the icons displayed in the social media bar. FirmenABC has neither influence nor access to cookies, which are set by Facebook, Twitter etc. In order to avoid that their personal data are transmitted to Facebook, Twitter etc. and assigned to their Facebook account, Twitter account, etc., users should log out of Facebook, Twitter etc. before visiting the website.
1.5. Change the cookie settings
How the web browser deals with cookies, which are allowed and denied, can be set by the user of a web browser. Where these settings are depends on the particular web browser. Detailed information can be retrieved via the help function of the respective web browser. If the use of cookies is restricted, it may not be possible to use all features of this website in full.
2. Data security
The person responsible takes technical and organizational security measures to protect the data stored by the provider against accidental or intentional manipulation, loss, destruction or against access by unauthorized persons.
3. Contradiction
You may object to the use and processing of your personal data at any time with effect for the future by an informal message. A deletion of stored personal data takes place as soon as you object to the use of your data or the purpose of the data collection has been fulfilled. Nevertheless, official or contractual retention requirements remain unaffected.
In the case of the existence of such duties, your data will be blocked for further use and automatically deleted after expiration of the retention period. You can also object to the use of cookies at any time by adjusting your browser settings accordingly.
Instructions can be found in the help pages of your browser manufacturer. As a service for you we link here to the instructions of common browser:
Microsoft Internet Explorer: Deleting and Managing Cookies - https://support.microsoft.com/deat/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies
Firefox: Block Cookies - https://support.mozilla.org/en/kb/Cookies-blocking
Google Chrome: Delete, enable and manage cookies in Chrome - https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647
4. Legal instruction
Affected parties are entitled to information, correction, deletion, limitation, data transfer, revocation and opposition. If incorrect data has been stored about you, we will correct it, of course. If you believe that the processing of your data violates the data protection law or your data protection claims have been violated in any way, you can complain to the data protection authority. You can request confirmation from us as to whether and to what extent we process your data.
Contact / Responsible according to imprint
Right to rectification: If we process your personal data which is incomplete or incorrect, you can at any time request its correction or its completion.
Right to cancellation: You may request the deletion of your personal data from us if we process it unlawfully or if the processing / publication of this data disproportionately interferes. Please note that there may be reasons opposing an immediate deletion, e.g. in the case of statutory storage requirements.
Right to restriction of processing: You may also request that we restrict the processing of your data, provided that you deny the accuracy of the data, for a period of time that allows us to verify the accuracy of the data, or the processing of the data Is unlawful, but you reject a deletion and instead require a restriction of data use, we no longer need the data for its intended purpose, but you still need this data to assert or defend legal claims, or you object to the processing of the Have entered data.
Right to Data Portability: You may require us to provide you with the information you have entrusted to us for safekeeping in a structured, common and machine-readable format, provided that we process this data based on a consent that you have given and may revoke, or for the performance of a contract between us, and this processing is done by automated means.
Right of objection: If we process your data for the purpose of exercising public duties or for the exercise of official authority or if we rely on the necessity of safeguarding our legitimate interest in processing, you can object to this data processing, provided that you have an overriding protection interest Data exists. The sending of advertising you can contradict at any time without giving reasons.
Right to complain: If you believe that we violate data protection laws when processing your data, we ask you to contact us in order to clarify any questions. Of course, you also have the right to complain to the data protection authority or to a supervisory authority within the EU.
Assertion of the rights: If you want to assert one of these rights to us, just use our contact options.
Confirmation of identity: In case of doubt, we may request additional information confirming your identity. This is to protect your rights and privacy.
Rights Excessive Fee: If you manifestly unfounded or very often perceive one of these rights, we may demand a reasonable processing fee or refuse to process your application.
SUPER
Wir freuen uns auf Ihre Kontaktaufnahme!
available lights Stefan Nemec Licht- & Filmgeräteverleih
Sebastian-Kohl-Gasse 3-9/19a
|
1210
Wien
+43 1 2719050
|
office@filmequipment.at
Impressum
|
Datenschutz
|
Wir freuen uns auf Ihre Kontaktaufnahme!
available lights Stefan Nemec Licht- & Filmgeräteverleih
Sebastian-Kohl-Gasse 3-9/19a
|
1210
Wien
+43 1 2719050
|
office@filmequipment.at
We are looking forward to your contact!
available lights Stefan Nemec Licht- & Filmgeräteverleih
Sebastian-Kohl-Gasse 3-9/19a
|
1210
Vienna
+43 1 2719050
|
office@filmequipment.at
Imprint
|
Privacy Policy
|
We are looking forward to your contact!
available lights Stefan Nemec Licht- & Filmgeräteverleih
Sebastian-Kohl-Gasse 3-9/19a
|
1210
Vienna
+43 1 2719050
|
office@filmequipment.at
Title
Um das Video der Firma available lights Stefan Nemec Licht- & Filmgeräteverleih mit Sitz in Wien abzuspielen, benötigen Sie ein Flash plugin in der Version 9.x oder höher.
